Guide to the Lewis and Clark Centennial and American Pacific Exposition and Oriental Fair Records 1894-1933
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Division of Exhibits (Henry E. Dosch), Series 9
  - Correspondence, General
    - Heckman, A. - Herring-Hall-Marvin, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/4)
      Herring-Hall-Marvin Safe Company
    - Herzong, Margaretta - Hirsch, Cal, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/5)
      Herzong, Margaretta
      Hess, Albert & Company
      Hetherington, J.
      Heustis, Bertha Lincoln
      Hewes, David
      Heymann, Eugene
      Hickey, M.J.
      Hill, Thomas G.
      Hilliker, B.F.
      Hills Brothers Company
      Himes, Geo H.
      Hines, J.M. (General Press Bureau)
      Hines, J.M. (Wilson, Wilson Company)
      Hirsch, Cal & Sons Iron & Rail Company
    - Hitt, J. M. - Hollander, J. H., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/6)
      Hitt, J.M.
      Hobbs, Oliver
      Hobbs, Vira E.
      Hoch, E.S.
      Hodgson, Ed
      Hoffman, August H.
      Hoffman, E.H.
      Holding, Mrs.
      Hollacher, G.A.
      Holland
      Hollander, J.H. (See also Anti-Selenite)
    - Holman, Edward - Hoosier Drill, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/7)
      Holman, Edward
      Holman, Frederick V.
      Holman, Herbert
      Holmes, E & B Machinery Company
      Holsinger, Leah (Ott Clothes Line Reel)
      Holyoke Belting Company
      Homer, H.F.
      Honeyman Hardware Company
      Hood River Development Company
      Hooke-Hardie Company
      Hoosier Drill Company
    - Hopf Brothers - Howarth, S., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/8)
      Hopf Bros.
      Hopkins, A.L.
      Horan Stay Hanger Company
      Horey, R.R.
      Horn, Gustavus A.
      Horn, J.G.
      Hough, Roland B.
      Hough, Romeyn
      Houser, J.O.
      Howard, J.W.
      Howard, Thos.
      Howarth, S.
    - Howe, Carrie - Hudson, John D., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/9)
      Howe, Carrie
      Howe, S.A.
      Howe, Wm. H.
      Howell, Edwin E.
      Howells, A.P.
      Hubbard, C.E.
      Hubbard & Fleischauler
      Hubbell, Ella A.
      Huber, Oskar
      Hudson, John D.
    - Hulbert, M. H. - Hyde, George E., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/10)
      Hulbert, M.H. (See also Johnson, Tom L.)
      Hulse, W.H.
      Hume, L.T.
      Hume Mercantile Company
      Humitsch, H.
      Hunt, Hamlin H.
      Hunt, T.K.
      Huntley Manufacturing Company
      Hurty, J.N. (Indiana State Board of Health)
      Hyatt, E.L.
      Hyde, Geo. E.
    - I-X-L Elastic - Inlaid Floor, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/11)
      I-X-L Elastic Truss Company
      Ideal Concrete Machinery Co.
      Ideal Specialty Company
      Illinois-Pacific Glass Company
      Independence Mining Company (C. B. Zeck)
      Indian School of Oregon
      Ingham, Maude M. (See also Rapid Remington Writer Company)
      Ingram, Maude H.
      Inlaid Floor Company
    - Innes, F. N. - Ivey, John, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/12)
      Innes, F.N. & His Band (see also series "General Files—Music," below)
      International Harvester Company
      International Mercantile Marine Company
      Irish Village
      Irrigation Publishing Company
      Irwin, Pearl
      Isaacs, Anna
      Ivery, T.H.
      Ivey, John
    - Jackson, Arthur C. - John Porteous, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/13)
      Jackson, Arthur C.
      Jackson, James (Portland Commercial Club)
      Jackson, Martin J.
      Jacoby, S.H.
      Jaeck, Emma
      Jaggy, J.H. Department Store
      James, Helen
      Jansen Lithographic Company
      Japan Paper Company
      Jaquet, F.G.
      Jargo, Q.B.
      Jewell, E.A.
      John Porteous Manufacturing Company
    - Johns, Charles - Johnson, William Pierce, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/14)
      Johns, Chas. C.
      Johnson, Andrew (Draft Rigging Model)
      Johnson, Ed M.
      Johnson, Emma
      Johnson, Geo. E.C.
      Johnson, H.A.
      Johnson, Lieber Company
      Johnson, Percy W.
      Johnson, Tom L.
      Johnson, W.E. (Motor extension Street sprinkler)
      Johnson, Wallace C.
      Johnson, William T.
      Johnson, Wm. Pierce
    - Johnston, J. C. - Jones, Edward John, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/15)
      Johnston, J.C.
      Johnston, K.I.
      Joliet Chair Company (See Frankfort Chair Company)
      Jones, Albert
      Jones, Alice
      Jones, Alice N.
      Jones, C.S.
      Jones, Clarence
      Jones, Edith L.
      Jones, Edward John
    - Jones, Elmer - Juvenile, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/16)
      Jones, Elmer
      Jones, Judson
      Jones, M.W.
      Jordon, E.B.
      Joy, Allan R.
      Judge Company
      Juvenile Merry-Go-Round Company
    - Kabo - Kellock, Julia, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/17)
      Kabo Corset Company
      Kaiser, E.J. (Valley Record)
      Kalekian, H.G.
      Kandall, H.F. (Reference Mr. Ramson
      Kansas City Southern Land & Immigration Company
      Kassabaum, Chas. H.
      Kastelic, G.A.
      Kathryns, Jas. R. (Pabst Brewing Company)
      Kaufer, Edward E.
      Kaufman, Alex
      Kelekian, H.G.
      Kellock, Julia
    - Kellogg, Francis B. - Kent, Joseph, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/18)
      Kellogg, Francis B.
      Kellogg Switchboard & Supply Company
      Kelly, Cleo
      Kelly, J.
      Kelly, Philip
      Kelly Plough Gasoline Locomotive Company
      Kemp, H.
      Kenfield Publishing Company
      Kennedy, E.N.
      Kennedy, W.
      Kent, B.F.
      Kent, Joseph
    - Kern, Joseph - Kimball, Frank William, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/19)
      Kern, Joseph
      Kernan, Frank T.
      Kerwin, Joe
      Ketchum, J.T.
      Keufel & Esser Company
      Keystone Jewelry Company
      Kibbe, Josephine B.
      Kiesel, Fred J. & Company (Groceries & Liquors)
      Kightlinger, E.E.
      Kilekian, H.G.
      Kimball, Frank Willard
    - King, Goodman - Knowlton, M. D., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/20)
      King, Goodman
      King, John H. (Inventor)
      Kingsbury, Geo. N.
      King’s Daughters and Sons
      Kirker, A. Julia
      Kiser, F.H.
      Kitchen, J.M.
      Klumpp, Wm.
      Knapp, Alma
      Knauer, E. (Manufacturers of the United States)
      Knowlton, M.D. Company
    - Kobe Chronicle - Krueger & Zapp, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/21)
      Kobe Chronicle, Japan
      Koken Barbers’ Supply Company
      Korona Light and Heat Company
      Kent's Gas Heater & Air Burner
      Krame, Tyler
      Krebs, Etta
      Krebs, Dr. R.
      Kremer, Eugenie
      Kremer, Victor Company
      Kroch Manufacturing Company
      Krueger & Zapp
    - Labels, list of - Lamberton, Harry W., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 66/22)
      Labels, list of
      Lackey, Jas. A.
      Ladd, W.M. Towle Syrup Company
      Ladies' Twentieth Century Novelty Company
      Laird & Lee Publishers
      Lake, E.R. (Professor)
      Lamb, Frank H., Timber Company
      Lamberson, Geo. H.
      Lambert, E.M.
      Lambert, James H.
      Lamberton, Harry W.
    - Lamont Corliss - Laundry Dryer, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/1)
      Lamont Corliss & Company
      Lamson Consolidated Store Service Company
      Landau Economic Syphon Company
      Landers Brothers Company
      Lane & Bodley Company
      Langfitt, W.C.
      Langford, Adelaide
      Lanyon, W.J.
      La Porte Carriage Company
      Larkin, Edgar L.
      Larsen Ice Machine Company
      Laundry Dryer & Heating Company
    - Lee, Benjamin - Lewis, William T., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/2)
      Lee, Benj. H.
      Lee Broom & Duster Company
      Lee, General Fitzhugh
      Lee, J.G. (Major)
      Leech, J. Annie
      Leleux, Keller (Electro Chermique)
      Leppel, Arthur S.
      Leschen, A. & Sons Rope Company
      Lewis and Clark Accommodation Bureau
      Lewis, L.W. (Honorable, Senator)
      Lewis, William T. (The Phonometric Institute)
    - Leyner, J. George - Lloyd, Edwin, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/3)
      Leyner, J. Geo.
      Liberati’s Grand Military Band (see also series "General Files—Music" below)
      Ligon, Greenwood
      Lilly, Bogardus and Company
      Lilly, Geo. W.
      Lind, Frederick H.
      Lindberg, Hans V.
      Lindley, S.
      Lindon Cereal Coffee Co.
      Lindsay, Evangeline
      Lindsey, J.L.
      Lippincott, J.B. Company
      Lloyd, Edwin
    - Locke, C. E. - Lownsdale, C. D., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/4)
      Locke, C.E.
      Lockmiller, Martin J.
      London and North-Western Railway of England
      Long, Chester I. (U.S. Senate)
      Longstreth, E.D.
      Lonn, Eleanor
      Lopp, W.T.
      Lothrop, J.H.
      Love, Mary V.
      Low, George P. (Electric Power & Gas)
      Lowell, J.P.
      Lowery, Geo. W.
      Lownes, Mariana (Norristown Covering Company)
      Lownsdale, C.D.
    - Luckey, Inez - Lystow, William, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/5)
      Luckey, Inez (Falls City, OR)
      Luckey, Inez (Sheridan, OR)
      Lueck, R.
      Luerzer, Feodore
      Luitwieler Pumping Engine Company
      Lusky, Col. S.
      Lussier, Will
      Lyons, Ed, Manager, North Pacific Terminal Company
      Lysell, F (Hemlandet Company)
      Lystow, Wm.
    - Mackey, Peter - Maeda, E. K., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/6)
      Mackey, Peter
      Mackey, S.P. (Knapp & Mackey Real Estate)
      MacDonald, G.
      MacKenzie, W.R.
      MacLaren, A.F. (Imperial Cheese Company)
      MacMullan, Jas.
      MacPheeters
      Macrae, A.C.
      Madeira, Francis P.
      Madison, F.R.
      Madison, Max C.
      Maeda, E.K.
    - Magill, F. B. - Manufacturers & Producers, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/7)
      Magill, F.B.
      Majestic Hotel and Bath House (See also Clark, John O'Fallon)
      Majestic Manufacturing Company
      Makeever, M.A.
      Malitz, Werner
      Mallmann Addograph Manufacturing Company
      Malmo & Company
      Malow, Wm.
      Manlove Gate Company
      Mann Speciality Company
      Manning, Maxwell and Moore
      Manufacturers' Association
      Manufacturers of the United States (See also Knauer, E.)
      Manufacturers & Producers Association
    - Marble Safety Axe - Marvin, Mae, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/8)
      Marble Safety Axe Company
      Markee Band & Orchestra
      Markham, E. (Kent Lumber Company)
      Marsbury, A.B. & Son
      Marshall Brothers Cement Contractors
      Marshall Wells Hardware Company
      Martin, A.W.
      Martin & Forbes
      Martin, J. Matte
      Marvin, Mae
    - Mason, William - Maxey, T., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/9)
      Mason, Wm.
      Massachusetts Institute of Technology
      Mast, Wm.
      Mathieu, J.P. and Company
      Mattheff, P.M.
      Matthews, Frederick D.
      Matthews-Northrup Works
      Matthews, Wm.B.
      Maurer, F.X. Company
      Maxey, T.
    - McAllen & McDonnell - McCoy, Mamie, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/10)
      McCabe, W.L.
      McCall, M.T.
      McCalley, R.B.
      McCann, Richard M. (Tandy-Wheeler Publishing Company)
      McCardle, J.M.
      McCarthy, Dennis
      McClair, Wm.
      McClellan, C.A.
      McComas, J.T.
      McComber, Warren
      McCorkle, J.W.
      McCoy, Mamie E.
    - McDaniel, E. A. - McKibbon, May E., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/11)
      McDaniel, E.A.
      McDaniel, E.W.
      McDermott, P.J. (Queensland, Australia)
      McDonnell, C.E. Major (Building Grounds)
      McDowell Company
      McGee, W.J. Dr.
      McGill, R.C.
      McGuigan, Geo. W.
      McKean-Zimmer & Company
      McKenzie, Chas. E. (McKenzie Novelty Company)
      McKibbon, May E.
    - McLean, A. C. - McVey, Frank L., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/12)
      McLean, A.C.
      McLeran, F.W (Wilhoit Hot Springs)
      McManigal, F. Herbert
      McMeekin, J.P.
      McNab & Smith
      McNutt, J. Davis
      McRae, Archie J.
      McRath, T.S.
      McRoberts, R.W.
      McSpadden, G.H.
      McVey, Frank.L.
    - Mears, W. A. - Melville, Geroge W., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/13)
      Mears, W.A.
      Measor, W.H.
      Meddaugh, J.E.
      Meehan, Fred J.
      Meier, Albert
      Meierhoff, Meta
      Meirill, Z.E.
      Melick, Chas. M.
      Mellis, F.R.
      Mellis, Fred
      Melton, Mary
      Melville, George W. (Publisher)
    - Mendelson Bros. - Miehle Printing, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/14)
      Mendelson Brothers
      Mendenhall, E.V.
      Merchants Express Company
      Merriman, W. (Southern Pacific Company)
      Merry, M.M.
      Merville, E.E. (See also Spencerian Commercial School)
      Metropolitan Improvement Company
      Metzger & Company
      Meyer-Tsutsumi Shokwai
      Middendorf, F.M.
      Middleton, M.S.
      Middleton Machine Company
      Middleton Motor Car Company
      Miehle Printing Press Manufacturing Company
    - Mikami, Y. - Mitchell, John H., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/15)
      Mikami, Y.
      Miles, S.A.
      Millard, P.A.
      Miller, Elsie
      Miller, George
      Miller, James Action
      Miller, H.B.
      Miller, R.B. (The Oregon Railroad & Navigation Company)
      Miller, W.O.
      Milton, Bradley and Company
      Milwaukee Dustless Brush Company
      Mindak Manufacturing Company
      Mitchell, C.W.
      Mitchell, John H (See also Oden, George J.)
    - Moffatt, H. W. - Moores, W. A., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/16)
      Moffatt, H.W. (Peerless Kitchen Boiler Company)
      Mohler, Geo. J.
      Moline Business Men's Association
      Moline Incandescent Lamp Company
      Moncure, W.A.P. (Professor)
      Montaigu, Countess de
      Montgomery, J.B.
      Montgomery Ward and Company
      Monton, S.A.
      Moody, R.E.
      Moore, E.J.
      Moore, W.C.
      Moore, W.H.
      Moores, Bertha
      Moores, W.A.
    - Morgan and Allen Co. - Moyer, I. W., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/17)
      Morgan and Allen Company
      Morgan Electric Machine Company
      Morgan, William D.
      Moriarty, D. (Patent Vase)
      Moritz, S.S.
      Morran, M.
      Morris, G. Harry
      Morris, J.H.
      Morris, M.J.
      Morris, W.H.
      Morse, G. Willis
      Mortensen, Ena
      Mortimer, C.H. Publishing Company
      Mory, L.H.
      Moyer, I.W.
    - Moulie, E. (perfumes), 1905 (Box-folder 67/18)
    - Muecke, G. - Mystic Shrine Gold & Copper, 1904-1906 (Box-folder 67/19)
      Muecke, G.
      Mueller, H. Manufacturing Company
      Mullenbeck, Tonie
      Mumford, A.W. (Publisher)
      Mungen & Morgan
      Munsell, B.E.
      Murphy, C.W. (Minnesota Swine Breeders Association)
      Murray Iron Works Company
      Musgrove, R.G.
      Musick, E.J.
      Mutual Label & Lithographic Company
      Myers, Horace C.
      Mystic Shrine Gold and Copper Mining Company
    - Nabarro, M. - National Sweeper, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/20)
      Nabarro, M.
      Nason, R.N. & Company (Oil and Paint)
      National Association of Automobile Manufacturers
      National Brazing Compound Company
      National Clock Works
      National Irrigation Congress
      National Pharmacy Company
      National and Providence Worsted Mills
      National Sweeper Company
    - Nebraska - Nilson, Carl J., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 67/21)
      Nebraska, State of
      Nelson & Makeever (Nelson Mandolin Orchestral)
      New Hampshire Commission
      Newell, Theresa
      Newhall, Chas.
      Newman, Myles and Company
      Newsham, D.
      Newton, C.G.
      Newton Gum Company
      Nichols, Dennis
      Nickey, Frank B. (Oil Properties)
      Nicolai Brother Company
      Niebel, Lizzie
      Niles-Bement-Pond Company
      Nilson, Carl J.
    - Norris Truss Co. - Nygren, Chris, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/1)
      Norris Truss Company
      Norsch, Frederick W.
      North Pacific Brewing Company
      North Wisconsin Farmers’ Association
      Northern Electrical Manufacturing Company
      Northwest Light & Water Company
      Northwestern Improvement Company (Storrs, L.S.)
      Northwestern Macaroni Company
      Northwestern School of Taxidermy
      Northwestern Yeast Company
      Nygren, Chris
    - O'Connor, J. J. V. - Opperman, Charles, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/2)
      O’Connor, J.J.V.
      O’Dea, Patrick J.
      Oden, George J. Lieut
      Office, The Men’s Record Company
      Ogilby, Charles
      Ohio Pottery Company
      Olberg, O.N.
      Olcott, Frances Jenkins
      Old Times Distillery Company
      Oliver, Maud I.G.
      Oliver, W.F.
      Omega Separator Company
      Opperman, Chas.
    - Oliver Typewriter Co., 1905-1906 (Box-folder 68/3)
    - Oregon Auto-Despatch - Ovens, William M., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/4)
      Oregon Auto-Despatch
      Oregon Burns Cottage Association
      Oregon Casket Company
      Oregon Railroad & Navigation Company (See also Craig, A.L.)
      Orr, George
      Orth, E.M.
      Ostrander, T.C.
      Otis Elevator Company
      Ott Clothes Line Reel
      Otten, George
      Ottke, August & Son (Oregon Tannery)
      Ovens, Wm.M.
    - Pacific Coast Biscuit - Pacific Tank Co., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/5)
      Pacific Coast Rubber Company
      Pacific Engineering Company
      Pacific Glass and Paint Company
      Pacific Hydraulic Press
      Pacific Light and Heat Company
      Pacific Rug Factory
      Pacific Spring Bed Company
      Pacific Tank Company
    - Page, J. E. - Patrick Cash Store, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/6)
      Page, J.E.
      Palmer, Floyd
      Palmer, Harry L.
      Palmer, Jessie Winston
      Palmer, Mary E.
      Palmer, Mary O.
      Palms, Madame
      Palouse Business Men’s Association
      Park, Austin T.
      Parker, W.D.
      Pasteur Vaccine Company Ltd.
      Patrick, Caroline G.
      Patrick Cash Store
    - Patterson, H. B. - Penrose, Stephen, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/7)
      Patterson, H.B. (Philippine Reservation)
      Patterson, W.J.
      Paul, W.A.
      Peck, E.E. and Company
      Peckard, C.C.
      Peck’s Tourist Bureau Company
      Peet, Jeanie S.
      Pendleton Woolen Mills
      Pennell, Thos. J.
      Pennington, Geo. W. Sons, Inc.
      Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts
      Pennsylvania Railroad Company
      Pennsylvania Salt Manufacturing Company
      Penrose, Stephen B.L. (Whitman College)
    - Perfection Spring Nut Co. - Pfiefer, Charles, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/8)
      Perfection Spring Nut Company
      Perkins, Charlton B.
      Perkins, H.C.
      Perley, G.A.
      Perry, C.S.
      Peters, John (Taxidermist)
      Peters & Reed Pottery Company
      Peterson, D. Ralph
      Pfaudler Company
      Pfeifer, Chas. H. ( The Tourist & Homeseeker Magazine)
    - 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/9)
      Phafler, Chas. H.
      Phelen, Chas.
      Philadelphia Commercial Museum
      Phillips, John J.
      Phoenix Iron Works
      Pierce, Dorothy
      Pioneer Implement Company
      Pioneer Paint Company
      Piper, E.B. ( The Oregonian)
      Pittsburg Novelty Manufacturing Company (See also Holsinger, Leah)
      Pittsburg Tubular Steel Whiffletree Company
      Platt Iron Works Company
      Plum, C.O.
      Plymouth Cordage Company
    - Pollard, E. M. - Post, P. W., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/10)
      Pollard, E.M.
      Pope-Gosser China Company
      Portland Chamber of Commerce
      Portland Commercial Club
      Portland Consolidated Railway Company
      Portland Cremation Association
      Portland Curled Hair Factory
      Portland Flouring Mills Company
      Portland Manufacturing Company
      Portland Rose Society (Frank Lee, Secretary)
      Portland Seed Company
      Porto Rico Company
      Post, Alfred H. and Company
      Post, P.W. (Metal Sawing Machines)
    - Potter, H. A. - Putnam, C. C., 1904-1906 (Box-folder 68/11)
      Potter, H.A. (Potter & Willard)
      Powell, Clinton N.
      Prather, L.H. (Seattle)
      Prather, L.H. (Spokane)
      Pratt, J.C.
      Preservaline Manufacturing Company
      Press Clipping Bureau
      Preston, Gertrude
      Price, E.M.
      Prouting, S.W.
      Prudential Insurance Company
      Public Ledger
      Puckett, Laura
      Purvine, S.E.
      Putnam, C.C. & Son (Putnam Spring Clothes Pin)
    - Quereau-Shrader - Quinn, Martin, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/12)
      Quereau-Shrader Selling Company
      Quick, H.C.
      Quigley, Samuel
      Quinn, Martin (General Blacksmith)
    - R. J. H. Co. - Ramsey, F. S., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/13)
      R.J.H. Company
      Rabbitt, J.A.
      Radek, J.
      Ragan, Jas. B.
      Rahr, William Sons' Company
      Railroad Supply Company
      Railway Appliances Company
      Railway Equipment Company
      Railway List Company
      Raley, J.H. (Carter and Raley)
      Ramsey, F.S.
    - Rand, Walter S. - Rarey, Benjamin, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/14)
      Rand, Walter S.
      Randall, T.P.
      Randall, Wm.E.
      Randalph Macon Women's College
      Rankin, S.B.
      Ransom, J.W. (Oregon Railroad & Navigation Company)
      Raphall, Iuna V.
      Rapid Economy Stamp Mill Company
      Rapid Remington Writer Company
      Rarey, Benj.
    - Reames, A. E. - Reeves, Charles M., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/15)
      Reames, A.E. (Deep Gravel Mining Company)
      Reasoner, F.K.
      Red Cross Antiseptic Mouth Piece Company
      Reddington & Company
      Redig, F. (Creamery Supply)
      Redington, Nellie F.M.
      Redmond, Granville
      Reed, A.J.
      Reed, Henry J.
      Reed, Merrill A.
      Reeve, Ferris E.
      Reeves, Chas. M.
    - Reid, Rena - Rice, Seth, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/16)
      Reid, Rena
      Rein, M.
      Reindahl, Knute
      Renner, John H.
      Replogle, J.E.
      The Republic
      Rhodes, Neva (Rhodes Drug Company)
      Rice M.H.
      Rice, Mollie
      Rice, Seth (Rev)
    - Richrds, H. T. - Ristdon Iron, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/17)
      Richards, H.T., San Diego-Eastern Railway Company
      Richards, L.B.
      Richardson, Carrie L.
      Richardson, G.B.
      Richardson, J.
      Richardson, Tom (Manager Portland Commercial Club)
      Riebhoff, M.N.
      Riedelsberger Music Studio
      Rieger, Paul L. & Company
      Riegle, P.A. (Dealer in Wool and Seeds)
      Ripberger, M.D. (Written in German)
      Ristdon, Iron and Locomotive Works.
    - Ritner, P. - Rocky Ford Mill, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/18)
      Ritner, P.
      Robards, J.E.
      Robb, W.A.
      Roberts, Johnson & Rand Shoe Company
      Roberts, W.R
      Robertson, Lulu (Victoria Public Schools)
      Robins Conveying Belt Company
      Rocamora, W. (European Novelty Company)
      Roche, Rose
      Rochester Fireworks Company
      Rochester Stamping Company
      Rocky Ford Mill and Elevator Company
    - Rodenkircher, Christian - Royal Novelty, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 68/19)
      Rodenkirchen, Christian A.
      Roeding, George C.
      Rogers, F.A.
      Rogers Locomotive Works
      Roll, August
      Romeyn, H.
      Root, A.T. Company
      Rosenberg, Ella C.
      Rosenthal, Charles M.
      Rouse, L.J.
      Rowe, E.J.
      Royal Novelty and Music Company
    - Rush, Allan C. - Ryan, W. F., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 69/1)
      Rush, Allan C.
      Russell, Hamlin (Russell's Convention Dates)
      Russell, S.W. (Clover Leaf Gold and Mining Company)
      Ruter, S.
      Rutherford, Maud Adair
      Ryan, Thomas F. (Judge)
      Ryan, W.F.
    - Sabin, Ellen C. - San Francisco Trade Journal, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 69/2)
      Sabin, Ellen C. (Milwaukee-Downer College)
      Sackett, Walter B. (Michigan Agriculture College)
      St. Louis Car Company
      St. Louis Fire Prevention Bureau
      St. Louis Shovel Company
      St. Paul’s German Evangelical Church (Rev. Richard Stave)
      Samson Iron Works
      Samuels, L. (Burnt Leather Goods)
      San Francisco Artificial Limb Company
      San Francisco Call
      San Francisco Chronicle
      San Francisco Timber Preserving Company
      San Francisco Trade Journal
    - Sanders, Alvin H. - Scanlan-Morris, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 69/3)
      Sanders, Alvin H. ( The Breeders Gazett)
      Sanders, Effie
      Sandwich Manufacturing Company
      Sanitary Street Sweeping Company
      Sanitol Chemical Laboratory Company
      Santelmann, W.H. (U.S. Marine Band)
      Sarrayarvi, Chas. (Cheese)
      The Sauer, C.F. (Flavoring Extracts)
      Saunders, William Flewellyn